One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's pile up all the dreams,
And go find the thing we're looking for... One Piece!
Compasses and the like will only slow us down
Delirious with fever, let's take the helm
Even an old treasure map covered in dust...
Isn't a legend if it's been proved real!
For our own storms, all we have to do is
Ride someone else's biorythm...
And pretend that it isn't there!
Let's pile up all the dreams,
and go find the thing we're looking for...
A pocket of coins, and
We are!
Let's break the tight-fisted night!
We have no interest in treasure chests
A pocket of romance, and
We are!
Let's pile up all the dreams,
And go find the thing we're looking for...
A pocket of coins, and
We are!
The Power That Can Deflect Anything?!
Zoro Fights Prepared to Die!
Hey, Zoro!
Robin!
Sanji!
Your bodies are vanishing!
Why?!
Didn't we win?!
Hey! Didn't we make it on time?!
She's disappearing!
Captain Lola!
Everyone!
Didn't we win?!
Damn it!
A pirate ship somewhere in the Grand Line
Captain!
Come to the deck for a moment, please!
Stop babbling nonsense and go back to sleep.
We will get erased by the morning sun if we step outside.
It's been two years since Moriah stole our shadows.
We no longer...
But Captain!
Take a look at my feet!
You have... your shadow!
My shadow's back!
Everyone else's too, Captain!
Everyone's shadows are back!
Captain, you don't think someone actually beat Moriah?
Don't be foolish.
That's impossible.
Moriah is a pirate who once fought against one of the Four Emperors, Kaido, or so I heard.
I can't think of a guy who could actually defeat him.
Grand Line, as well as various places in West Blue
I've got my shadow back!
It's been such a long time since I last saw the sunlight!
Our zombies at Thriller Bark must have been destroyed!
Moriah's curse has been lifted!
Boss!
I see the morning sun!
Look at my shadow!
My shadow is following me!
My reflection is in the mirror!
Hey, what was that noise, Margarita?!
My shadow!
My shadow is back!
What?
You got your shadow back?
Your shadow that was stolen by pirates over ten years ago?!
It's true.
Master, please forgive me!
I was so surprised that I dropped the family heirloom plates!
I had a grudge against them, but not anymore.
I didn't mean to break them.
I'm terribly sorry.
I'll leave the mansion immediately.
What're you talking about?
They were just some plates after all.
Did you get hurt?
Anyway, let's celebrate.
I'm so happy for you, Margarita.
Aren't you happy?
Yes!
Thriller Bark
It seems we're alive.
For a moment, I felt like I was going to heaven.
That's fine!
I wouldn't mind going to heaven as long as it's with Robin-chan!
This isn't funny, you idiots!
We really thought you were dead! You were vanishing into thin air!
What a scary view.
The morning sun!
We don't have to fear the sun anymore!
We have our shadows!
Our days in that gloomy forest are finally over!
All right!
Everyone over there seems fine as well.
Our existence was erased for a moment, when the sun shone upon us.
But at the last second, our shadows returned. Thus our bodies were regenerated.
It's just like Moriah said when he transformed the shadow to change the body's shape.
As far as I understand, shadow and body must have the same shape.
Take it easy.
Never again will your shadow and body be separated in such a strange way.
Anyway, I'm glad no one was completely erased.
I feel sleepy all of a sudden.
Does anyone have cola?
All these weird creatures we've come across since we entered this island...
Were merely illusions created by Moriah.
Now that he's gone, there's nothing left on the island.
Everything disappears, like the morning after waking up from a nightmare.
Truly a devilish haunted mansion.
Wake up!
Absalom!
Hey, wake up!
Lola!
Don't panic.
It no longer has a shadow.
Hogback.
What happened to me?
I have no idea what happened to you.
Beaten by someone I assume, pathetic.
More importantly, Moriah-sama was-
What?!
Moriah-sama was beaten by Straw Hat?!
Don't talk so loud!
Be quiet!
You're too loud!
Thriller Bark is nothing but a worthless pile of rubble now.
But I don't plan on spending my days as a loser!
What about you?
Me?
Didn't Luffy's body shrink a while ago?
Luffy's body shrinks for a moment as a side effect of that Giant Gear.
His new techniques are too much for his body, aren't they?
The stronger the enemies we encounter, the more reckless this guy will get.
If we keep going like this...
A zombie!
So there was still one left?!
No, just a heavily injured old man.
No way! You're practically a zombie!
It's that geezer we met at the graveyard.
I don't believe it.
I didn't think the day would come when we could walk under the sun again.
Thank you so much!
How can we ever repay this favor!
Hey! Old man Spoil!
Old man!
President of the victim association!
Oh! You guys are fine too?
Yes, are you?
Yes.
You know each other?
By the way, you two, where's your gratitude?
We too, thank you from the bottom of our hearts!
I apologize for all the sudden meddling and all!
It's just that when we saw you guys rampaging, we decided to take a chance, and place our hopes in you!
Thank you very much!
I speak for everyone in the Thriller Bark Victim Association when I say...
We will never forget this debt!
Thank you very much!
Feel free to ask for anything!
Though it's not much, we have plenty of food.
In return, you can marry me.
Hell no!
You keep thanking us, but...
Don't say that!
It's like Luffy said, old man.
You there!
We had our own reasons for fighting.
Won't you marry me?!
We just happened to help you by accident.
What're you saying?!
If they want to thank us so badly, then let them do it!
That's right, bro!
Ask anything you want!
Whether it was an accident or not, we're very grateful you defeated Moriah!
Is that so?
Um... Your eyes...
That's right! I completely forgot about it!
What's the matter?
I forgot about him!
Is something wrong?
We're in big trouble!
I see.
So it turned out as I feared.
It appears so.
Who's that over there?
He's here.
Stay calm and listen.
I didn't want to bring this up while in the middle of the battle with Moriah, but...
On this island...
There was another...
Warlord of the Sea!
What did you just say?!
That's a...
Warlord of the Sea?!
Just when we finally found a replacement for Crocodile.
We can't afford to have another empty gap in the Warlords.
Is there still breath in him?
Who knows.
As long as there's a breath of life in him,
we will wait for his recovery and allow him to take up his place as a Warlord again.
We'll worry about that later.
If we keep losing one after another, the dignity of the Warlords will end up disappearing.
We can't let this information get spread around the world.
Seriously, what a bunch of troublemakers.
It's true... Even Moriah falls short of that giant's size,
That pirate known as "The Tyrant",
Bartholomew Kuma.
He is Kuma the Tyrant?!
Do you understand what I'm saying?
There must not be any witnesses of Moriah's defeat.
This is a direct order from the World Government...
The Straw Hat crew, along with any survivors on the island must be...
eliminated.
Simple enough.
What was that just now?!
Did he say "eliminated"?!
Hey, hey! Eliminate...
Us?!
Why?!
I can't believe this is happening!
Just when we finally got free from Moriah's power!
No way!
We have to fight two Warlords consecutively?!
You guys, step back.
I'll handle this!
Be careful!
He's got some sort of ability!
He completely let a person vanish just by touching her with his hand!
H-He vanished a person just by touching them?!
S-So scary!
Plus, he can move instantly from one location to another!
Those hands are dangerous!
What?!
He's here!
He's huge!
When did he-
Dammit! Just when we finally got our freedom!
Like I'm gonna die in this place!
That's right! We won't let anyone get in our way anymore!
Everyone, get him!
Yes, yes! Get him!
Stop it, you fools!
You're no match for him!
Even the guys who weren't touched were pierced by something.
Pirate Hunter Zoro.
I'll start with you.
Hey, hang in there!
Are you okay?
What the hell did he do?!
Something went through him without touching him!
That's his ability?
What a cruel thing to do.
Just when we finally managed to break free from our suffering in Moriah's forest after so many years.
We don't even have the chance to celebrate before another Shichibukai shows up to exterminate us all.
This isn't fair!
You don't know what the Straw Hats went through to finish this battle!
We will fight in their place, regardless of the odds!
Even if our enemy is a Warlord!
You're not as tough as Moriah or Oars anyways!
Shut up and stay back!
He's after me, didn't you hear him?
I'll take him on.
I don't need your help.
Don't humiliate me.
You people have quite a reputation.
Straw Hat's ship sure is full of exceptional people.
This isn't the time to feel flattered!
You've caused too many disturbances.
It's not just your captain; your whole crew has become quite noteworthy.
Hey, Zoro, wait!
Don't be reckless!
You're completely worn out, aren't you?!
When it rains, it pours; disasters hit one after another.
It's not like anything will change if we complain.
If I die here, it means this is as far as I could go!
Two Sword Style...
Draw and Resheath Technique!
Castle Gate!
What the hell was that?!
Look! It didn't even touch him and he's already hurting!
What is his ability?!
What's that mark he left in the rubble?!
Look! His palm!
A p-paw?!
How can a human have paws?
36 Pound Cannon!
Look out!
He deflected Zoro's attack with his hand!
How can he do that?!
So that's your ability.
The power to deflect anything.
I'm a paw-man with the power of the Paw Fruit.
A-A paw-man?!
That sounds so harmless.
Are there more lamely named fruits out there?
I dunno whether he's a Warlord or a charitable guy, but...
We're probably overestimating this guy.
Franky!
Cyborg Franky.
Is that all you have to offer?
He might be deflecting the air...
Mere artillery is useless against Franky.
It's called Pad Cannon.
The air deflected at the speed of light generates a powerful shock wave that can pierce through anything.
Your time's up.
Swift Pad Cannon!
Streaming Wolf Blades!
Zoro!
He repelled even that attack!
You!
It’s useless!
He can't keep this up!
It's a miracle that he can even fight in that condition!
He took enough damage to kill a normal human just from that monster Oars!
Zoro, behind you!
Run!
Zoro!
That's as far as you go!
Concasse!
Grind
Sanji!
Try deflecting that with your paws!
Your skull must've been smashed to bits, bastard!
Bastard, mind your own...
Black Leg Sanji.
So that's you.
He didn't even falter from Sanji's kick.
What's going on?
What's with his toughness?!
Is his face made of steel?!
F-F-Fire Bird Star!
King of the Snipers.
What an outrageous alias.
I have no interest in destroying you all when you are in such a worn-out state.
My mission is to exterminate every single one of you, but...
What is he doing?
The air...
Is he compressing the air with his paws?
It's getting smaller.
By deflecting the atmosphere with his paws he's pressurizing lots of air, condensing it more and more.
The power of that much condensed air, trying to return to its former size...
Will without a doubt generate a massive shock wave.
Just like a bomb.
W-What?
A bomb?!
You mean he's creating a bomb?!
I will spare your lives.
But in exchange,
I want you to bring me Straw Hat Luffy's head.
As long as they have him, the government won't mind.
Betray our comrade...?!
Now, bring him to me.
We refuse!
Such a shame.
Ursus Shock.
Lion's Song!
What the hell are you?!
A cyborg, just like Franky?!
No. His body is even harder than steel!
He melted the steel...
Cyborg.
That's certainly true.
But I'm completely different from Cyborg Franky.
I'm what is called a Pacifista.
A human weapon from the government that is yet to be completed.
Pacifista?
I was developed by the government's genius scientist.
Dr. Vegapunk.
He is the most brilliant person in the world.
It is said his knowledge is 500 years ahead of our time.
So he possesses such a body, and he's a Devil's Fruit user!
I can't hope to beat that.
And as expected, I can no longer move.
Is there anything I can do to stop you from taking Luffy's head?
That's as far as I can negotiate.
I understand.
Then, go ahead and take it...
But...
Not his head!
I beg you to take my life instead of his!
I may not be as worthy as him yet, but...
The head of the man who would one day become the strongest swordsman...
Isn't bad either!
Even with such an ambition, you'd sacrifice yourself for this man?
The way I see it, this is the only way to help the crew.
How can I protect my ambition when I can't even protect my captain!
Luffy's the man who is gonna be the Pirate King!
Hold it, hold it, you bastard!
What'll happen if you die?
What about your ambition, idiot?
Hey, big guy!
Hey!
Forget this moss-head swordsman.
Take my life instead!
The Marines are still taking me lightly, but...
Before long, the one who's bound to become the most dangerous person in this crew is...
Me, Black-Leg Sanji!
What're you waiting for?
I'm prepared to exchange my life for his!
The flower of my glorious death shall bloom on this spot.
Hey, make sure to...
Say goodbye to everyone for me.
Tell them I'm sorry, but they'll have to look for a new cook.
W-Why you!
That's my last request.
If I were to claim Straw Hat's life after this, I'd feel ashamed.
I'm in your debt.
Trust me in what I'm about to do,
I'll keep my promise no matter what.
But in exchange, I will make you...
Experience hell itself.
What I just extracted from his body is his pain and fatigue.
All the damage he accumulated during his battle with Moriah is within this.
If you really intend to take his place, then you must literally share his suffering.
Adding such damage to your current condition will eliminate your chances of survival.
It will be certain death.
Have a taste.
How was it?
Please let me... do this somewhere else!
He has good friends.
As expected from your son,
Dragon.
Hey! Is everyone alright?!
He was so sure that attack would be enough to exterminate us all that he didn't even check if it did!
Take that, stupid bear-man!
That hurts.
Hey, hey, are you kidding me?
What happened to you?
Hey look, my body is as light as a feather!
I dunno why!
Liar, that's not possible!
Maybe he took so much damage that now he feels fine.
It's not as simple as that!
Where did that idiot go?!
There he is.
You sure scared me for a second.
Hey, where did that Warlord-
What's with all this blood!?
Hey!
Hey, are you alive?!
Where is he?!
What the hell happened here?!
No-
Nothing...
at all!
Translation & initial timing, Vegapunk
Timing, Galaxy 9000, , Time-checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil, Galaxy 9000, Halee
Soundtracking, Halee
Video editing, Sewil
Raw provider, SOFCJ-Raws